You
He
Let me down easily
You're too light, you're too light
Don't you pray, don't you pray
You're seeking for my embrace
Wanting my dust begging me to stay
Every night and day
Call my name, shout it till you break
You took my heart
Held it and ran to the park
Made me a prisoner
Got me going round the
Feel it that you found
Fuddled me again
Not until I spent
Taking my own land
God's happy me
Oh, get over my doubt
Don't I get it without
For a year right now
Look at my way, look at my way
I want to know the cure
For at that time you made me endure
All the words you say
I'll keep your people at the head
I work in this town
Ready my love, one dance
Taking me leaping
Getting far away from your cheetah
Sicking for my embrace
Wanting my dust begging me to stay
Every night and day
Callin' mine up, shut it till you break
You took my heart
Held it and ran to the park
Made me a prisoner
Got me going round the
Feel it that you found
Fuddled me again
Not until I spent
Taking my own land
God's happy me
Oh, get over my doubt
Thought I can live without
For I get right now
Look at my way, look at my way
I want to know the cure
For at that time you made me endure
No need to waste that
Take it back and lay
Go something new
Get over my doubt
Thought I can live without
For I get right now
I'm telling you I'll kill for you
Like a fool, we know who
Never was a dog in the face
You'll pull ever make me ill
We knew that I could fall in
Feel, cry, feel, make you proud
What I feel, wish you well
I'd be grand again
Then I'd be able to live
Tell you I'll kill for you
Like a fool, we know who
Never was a dog in the face
You'll pull ever make me ill
We knew that I could fall in
Feel, cry, feel, make you proud
What I feel, wish you well
I'd be grand again
Then I'd be able to live
Tell you I'll kill for you